Register to The Kay Swift Papers
Yale University Music Library
- Music, 1911-1986; Series I; 4.6' (11 boxes)
  - Stage Works, I.A
    - [Little show. Can't we be friends?, arr.] Dick Hyman plays "Avalon" and "Can't we be friends?": complete note-for-note transcriptions of two classic jazz piano solos / words by Paul James; music by Kay Swift -- Katonah: Ekay Music, 1987., 29 p. of music; 28 cm. (Box 4, Folder 103)
      2 versions: Can't we be friends?: introductory reharmonization by Dick Hyman (p. 6-7)-- Can't we be friends? with "Believe me if all those endearing young charms": an improvisation by Dick Hyman (p. 8-14)
      Inscription inside front cover: to Kay- with great admiration! Dick Hyman.
    - [Never a dull moment], 1 manuscript vocal score (various pagings); various sizes. (Box 4, Folder 104)
      For the 1950 film starring Irene Dunn and Fred MacMurray based on Kay Swift's book about her second marriage, Who Could Ask for Anything More? (1943)
      Contents (in alphabetical order): Dance pantomime: "Nightmare in the desert" (5 p.). Down crooked river way (3 p.) [on page 1 in pencil: One day we'll buy back the number RKO did not use. See film + count bars used of "Sagebrush Lullaby"]. Gate to nowhere (3 p.). He's a pretty fair hand (4 p.). Me and my jam-up friend (5 p.). Once you find your guy (3 p.). Sagebrush lullaby (3 p.). Some of the time I'll miss you (3 p.) [note on page 1: Written for "Who Could Ask" (Never A Dull Moment)]
    - [Never a dull moment. Once you find your guy], 1 manuscript part (2 p.); 32 cm. (Box 4, Folder 105)
    - [Never a dull moment. Once you find your guy] Once you find your guy / words and music by Kay Swift -- New York: Harms, 1950., 1 vocal score (5 p.); 31 cm. (Box 4, Folder 106)
    - [Never a dull moment. Sagebrush lullaby (Sketches)], 1 leaf of music; 32 cm. (Box 4, Folder 107)
    - [Nine-fifteen revue. Opening] Opening., 1 manuscript piano score (2 p.); 32 cm. (Box 4, Folder 108)
      At top of page 1: 9:15.
    - [Nine-fifteen revue. Up among the chimney pots] Up among the chimney-pots / music by Kay Swift; lyrics by Paul James., 1 manuscript vocal score (3 p.); 32 cm. (Box 4, Folder 109)
      Holograph (?) in ink, annotations in pencil and ink, and pinned on.
    - [Nine-fifteen revue. Up among the chimney pots] Up among the chimney pots / Kay Swift; Paul James., 1 manuscript part (1 p.); 32 cm. (Box 4, Folder 110)
    - [Nine-fifteen revue. Up among the chimney pots] Up among the chimney pots / music by Kay Swift; words by Paul James -- New York: Harms, 1930., 1 vocal score (5 p.); 31 cm. (Box 4, Folder 111)
    - [Nothing is too lovely to be true] Nothing is too lovely / music & lyrics by Kay Swift ASCAP., 1 manuscript condensed score (various pagings); 36 cm. (Box 5, Folder 112)
      Written for the Clairol Carousel at the 1964-65 New York World's Fair.
      Contents: Nothing is too lovely (Part I :30) (2 p.). Nothing too lovely-part 1/45 (3 p.). Vocal verse-part II (2 p.). B.G. part III (4 p.). 45sec BG and vocal tag part V (2 p.). Orch. ending :30 part VI (1 p.). Orch. ending: 45 part VI (2 p.)
      Vocal verse-part II dated: 4/11/64.
      B.G. part III dated: 4/11/64.
    - [Nothing is too lovely to be true] Nothing is too lovely to be true / music and lyrics by Kay Swift., 1 manuscript vocal score (4 p.); 36 cm. (Box 5, Folder 113)
      2 copies, 1 negative photostat with annotations.
    - [Nothing is too lovely to be true] Nothing is too lovely to be true / music and lyrics by Kay Swift., 1 manuscript vocal score (3 p.); 32 cm. (Box 5, Folder 114)
    - [Nothing is too lovely to be true], 1 manuscript part (1 p.); 32 cm. (Box 5, Folder 115)
    - [Nothing is too lovely to be true (Sketches)], 3 leaves of music; 32 cm. (Box 5, Folder 116)
    - [One little girl] Camp Fire Girls' overture / Kay Swift; arr. Hans Spialek., 1 manuscript score (various pagings); various sizes. (Box 26, Folder 714)
      Order for this and subsequent entries is derived from script in 13/48.
      Contents: Camp Fire Girl's overture (26 p.).Between age (utility) (7 p., last p. is a fragment). Fughetta (theme for mother) (6 p.). Bicycle melos (3 p.). In-between-age I (7 p.). In-between-age [Linda's theme song] (12 p.). Camp fire cookout (19 p.). Apparition (1 p.). My favorite Camp Fire Girl (2 versions, 5 p., 6 p.). Such fun melos (3 p.). She used to be such fun [Julie's song] (2 versions, 9 p., 9 p.) [1 version marked: Version for the show]. When you ride your bike (17 p.). Favorite girl melos (3 p.). Wedding bell (2 p.). Indian finale (13 p.). Astronaut theme (7 p.). Lunar theme (6 p.). Moon clown (10 p.). Interview on the moon [Is the earth blue?] (26 p.). Camp fire processional (8 p.). Processional finale (9 p.). In-between-age reprise (6 p.)
    - [One little girl] Music and lyrics for production of Camp Fire Girls / Kay Swift., 1 manuscript vocal score (various pagings); various sizes. (Box 5, Folder 117)
      Holograph in pencil and ink, annotations in ink.
      Found in envelope marked: Originals (pencil) and some ink copies MUSIC and LYRICS for "One Little Girl" Kay Swift, 1960 Note: This is the show with book by Gilbert Seldes, Doris Frankel + Alfred Stern for Camp Fire Girls, inc., produced by Alfred Stern Starring Paul Hartman Featuring Louise Carlyle Frances Underhill William Johnstone and George W. Jones Camilla Ashley Willard Swire choreographer: Lewis DaPron [some of this information does not correspond to program]
      Contents: Overture (6 p.). Astronaut (2 p.) [note at top of page 1: part of which is also used in "moon" opening]. Fughetta (Theme for "Mother") (2 p.). In-between-age (4 p.) [annotations in ink]. Camp fire cookout (2 versions, 4 p., 10 p.). My favorite Camp Fire Girl (3 p.). She used to be such fun (4 p.). When you ride your bike (4 p.). Interlude between 1st + 2nd choruses of "Bike" (1 p.). Indian dance A (2 p.). Indian dance (B) (2 p.). Square dance (4 p.) [annotations pasted in]. Square dance (after 2nd chorus of "Cookout") (3 p.). Added section for square dance (4 p.). When you hear a song in waltz time (3 p.). Lunar theme (2 p.). Moon clown (3 p.). Interview on the moon (10 p.). Camp fire processional (4 p.)
    - [One little girl], 1 manuscript vocal score (various pagings); various sizes. (Box 5, Folder 118)
      Holograph (negative and positive photostats [1 page is original]), annotations in pencil, ink, and attached.
      Some music found in folder marked: K.S. [ORIGINAL PIANO COPIES, (crossed out)] NEGATIVES [AND 1 (ONE) PHOTOSTATIC COPY (crossed out)] OF EACH SONG FOR CAMP FIRE GIRLS, INC. [(IF REQUESTED). (crossed out)] 3 (THREE) SONGS WITH WORDS "CAMP FIRE" IN THE TITLE WERE DELIVERED TO CAMP FIRE GIRLS, INC., AS PER CONTRACT, FOR CAMP FIRE COPYRIGHT. [arrow from 3 (THREE)... to] Plus "Square Dance" (Part of "Cookout); LUNAR THEME MOON CLOWN ASTRONAUT THEME FUGHETTA THEME (FOR "MOTHER" WHEN YOU HEAR A SONG IN WALTZ TIME.
      Contents: Astronaut theme (part of which is also used in "Moon" opening) (2 p.). Fughetta (Theme for "Mother") (2 p.). In-between-age (4 p.). Camp fire cookout (2 versions, 10 p., 4 p.) [note attached: OLD VERSION SEE SMALLER NEG. STAT]. My favorite Camp Fire Girl (3 p. + 1 p. [holograph in pencil]). She used to be such fun (4 p.). When you ride your bike (4 p.). When you hear a song in waltz time (2 p.). Lunar theme (2 p.). Moon clown (3 p.). Interview on the moon (10 p.). Camp fire processional (4 p.)
    - [One little girl], 1 manuscript condensed score (various pagings); 32 cm. (Box 5, Folder 119)
      Contents: Camp Fire Girl's overture (12 p.). In-between-age (5 p.). My favored [sic] camp fire girl (3 p.). When you ride your bike (7 p.). Astronaut theme (4 p.). Moon clown (5 p.). Interview on the moon (11 p.). Camp fire processional (4 p.). Processional finale (4 p.). In-between age-reprise (3 p.)
    - [One little girl], 1 manuscript vocal score (various pagings); 32 cm. (Box 5, Folder 120)
      Copyist's manuscript (photocopy [1 page is original]), annotations in pencil, ink, and attached.
      Contents: In-between age (4 p.). Camp fire cookout (9 p.). My favorite Camp Fire Girl (4 p.). She used to be such fun (2 copies, 3 p., 3 p. + 1 p. [holograph in pencil]). Indian dance (A) (2 p.). Indian dance (B) (2 p.). Added section for square dance (4 p.)
    - [One little girl], 12 manuscript parts (various pagings); 32 cm. (Box 5, Folder 121)
      Holograph in ink, annotations in red and blue pencil, and ink.
      Contents: Camp fire cookout (2 versions, 1 p., 1 p.). My favorite Camp Fire Girl (1 p.). She used to be such fun (1 p.). When you ride your bike (2 versions, 2 p., 2 p). When you hear a song in waltz time (1 p.). Interview on the moon (4 versions, 2 p., 2 p., 2 p., 1 p.). Camp fire processional (1 p.)
    - [One little girl. (Sketches)], 7 leaves of music; 32 cm. (Box 5, Folder 122)
      Includes: "Bridge" of Linda's theme. "Bridge" for Linda's arrival on moon. Two on a bicycle. Be such fun in C - In between - A-flat (3 p.)
    - [One little girl. In-between-age] In between-age / music and lyrics by Kay Swift A.S.C.A.P., 1 manuscript vocal score (3 p.); 32 cm. (Box 5, Folder 123)
      At bottom of page 1: Copyright 1960 by KAY SWIFT.
      Sole Selling Agent: SAMSON MUSIC COMPANY 400 E 59th ST., New York, N.Y. [same as information appearing on published music in 5/124.]
    - [One little girl. In-between-age] In-between-age / music and lyrics by Kay Swift -- New York: Samson, 1960., 1 vocal score (2 p., 3 copies); 31 cm. (Box 5, Folder 124)
      At top of page 1: PROFESSIONAL COPY.
    - [One little girl. In-between-age. Reprise] In-between age - reprise., 1 manuscript condensed score (3 p.) + 27 manuscript parts; 32 cm. (Box 5, Folder 125)
      Condensed score of Hans Spialek's orchestration (see 25/713)
      Found in folder marked: IN-BETWEEN-AGE (version on side 2, band 5, of album) Music and lyrics Kay Swift orchestration Hans Spialek.
      Parts for: flute (2 verions), clarinet (2 versions), trumpet I (2 versions), trumpet II (2 versions), trombone (2 versions), percussion (3 copies), violin I (4 copies), violin II (3 copies), viola (2 versions), violoncello (2 versions), double bass (2 verisions), and voice
      Voice part is holograph in ink, annotations in red and blue pencil.
    - [One little girl. Square dance (Sketches)], 4 leaves of music; 32 cm. (Box 5, Folder 126)
      4 types of manuscript scores exist for this work, none of which comprises a complete score: copyist's manuscript vocal score in ink, on transparencies (5/127); copyist's manuscript vocal score (photocopy) (5/128); copyist's manuscript piano score in ink (some photocopy) (5/129); holograph and copyist's manuscript piano score [1 is vocal score] (photocopy) (5/130). In addition there are holograph and copyist's manuscripts of individual songs.
      The following order is suggested by the numbering and annotations on some of these manuscripts, some of which is conflicting (numberings and folders indicated):
      Overture [1] (5/129). The waltz I heard in a dream (in overture) [1] (5/127, 5/128). Nou-nou [2] (5/127, 5/128, 5/129). Black out "nou nou" [2A] (5/128).
      A lady of fashion [3] (5/127, 5/128, 5/130). [Untitled [3B] (5/129).] The duchess of Verprés [4] (5/127, 5/128).
      La belle conchita [5] (5/127, 5/128, 5/129, 5/130). Oh look mon trésor [5C] (5/129). La bicyclette [6] (1/127, 1/129, 1/130). Bicyclette finale [6A] (5/129).
      The angel [8] (5/127, 5/128, 5/130 [16]). The laundress [9] (5/127, 5/128). Tourne mon moulin [9A] (6/154).
      Boston school teacher [10] (5/127, 5/128, 5/129, 5/130 [19]). A woman of virtue [11] (5/127, 5/128). Lend me a bob till Monday [11C (11B crossed out)] (5/127, 5/128).
      A professor's wife [12] (5/129). Avec mes sabots [12A] (5/129). [Folk song (12, 12A)] (5/127, 5/128, 5/130).
      Entr'acte II [13] (5/129). La goulue [14] (5/127, 5/128). Goulue cues [14A] (5/129). Can-can [Playbill indicates this position within the order.] (5/127, 5/128). Lion tamer [Calliope] [15] (5/127, 5/128, 5/129). Calliope (interlude) [probably follows 15] (5/127, 5/128).
      Waltz [The waltz I heard in a dream] [16] (5/127, 5/128, 5/130 [10, 11], labeled Berthe la sourde). The waltz I heard in a dream [probably 16] (5/127, 5/128). Quarrel music [16B] (5/127, 5/128). Peaceful theme [16D] (5/127, 5/128, 6/151 [this version follows Folk song (12, 12A)]).
      Berthe la sourde [16F] (5/129). Yvette [17] (5/127, 5/128, 5/129). Saint Lazare [17A] (5/128, 6/152). Madame Arthur [17B] (5/128, 6/149). Exit [18] (5/129).
      [Order unknown: The house where I was born (6/146) (somewhere between Calliope and Mme. Arthur)]
      This order is observed for all entries, minus omissions, with the exception of 5/130.
    - Paris '90
      - [Paris '90], 1 manuscript vocal score (various pagings); 32 cm. (Box 5, Folder 127)
        Copyist's manuscript in ink, on transparencies.
        Printed at bottom of transparencies: Arnold Arnstein.
        Contents: The waltz I heard in a dream (in overture) (3 p.). The nou nou (2 p.). A lady of fashion (2 p.). The duchess of Verprés (1 p.). La belle conchita (4 p.). La bicyclette (2 p.). The angel (2 p.). The laundress (2 p.). A Boston schoolteacher (4 p.). A woman of virtue (2 p.). Lend me a bob till Monday (2 p.). Folk song (1 p.) [at top of page: TRADITIONAL ARR. BY KAY SWIFT]. La goulue (2 p.). Can-can (2 p.). Calliope (6 p.). Calliope (interlude) (6 p.). Waltz [The waltz I heard in a dream] (2 p., page 2 is a fragment). The waltz I heard in a dream (3 p.) [annotations in ink]. Quarrel music (2 p.). Peaceful theme (2 p.). Yvette (3 p., lacks 2-3)
      - [Paris '90], 1 manuscript vocal score (various pagings); various sizes. (Box 5, Folder 128)
        Copyist's manuscript (photocopy), annotations in pencil, ink, red and blue pencil, pasted in, and attached.
        Printed at bottom of paper: Arnold Arnstein.
        Contents: The waltz I heard in a dream (in overture) (3 p., 2 copies). The nou nou (2 p.). A lady of fashion (2 p.). The duchess of Verprés (1 p.). La belle conchita (4 p., lacks p. 1-2). The angel (2 p.). The laundress (2 p.). A Boston schoolteacher (4 p.). A woman of virtue (2 p.). Lend me a bob till Monday (2 p., 2 copies). Folk song (1 p.) [at top of page 1: TRADITIONAL ARR. BY KAY SWIFT]. La goulue (2 p.). Can-can (2 p.) [at top: overture]. Lion tamer [Calliope] (2 copies, 7 p., 6 p). Calliope (interlude) (6 p., 3 copies). Waltz [The waltz I heard in a dream] (2 p., 2 copies). The waltz I heard in a dream (3 p.). Quarrel music (2 p.). Peaceful theme (2 p., 2 copies). Yvette (3 p., 2 copies). Saint lazare (4 p.). Madame Arthur (8 p.).
      - [Paris '90], 1 manuscript piano score (various pagings); various sizes. (Box 5, Folder 129)
        Copyist's manuscript in ink (some photocopy), annotations in pencil, and red and blue pencil.
        Some have instrumental cues.
        On first page of all scores: Piano.
        Contents: Overture (11 p.). Nou-nou (includes Blackout "nou nou") (4 p.). [3B (2 p.)]. La belle conchita (3 p.). Oh look mon trésor (1 p.). La bicyclette (2 p.). Bicyclette finale (3 p.). [Boston] School teacher (5 p.). A professor's wife (2 p.). Avec mes sabots (2 p.). Entr' acte II (5 p.). Goulue cues (5 p.). Lion tamer [Calliope] (5 p.). Berthe la sourde (4 p.). Yvette (3 p.). Exit (6 p.). [1 page unidentified]
      - [Paris '90], 1 manuscript piano score (various pagings); 28 cm. (Box 5, Folder 130)
        Holograph (photocopy [1 is copyist's manuscript]), annotations in pencil and red pencil.
        Numbering contradicts other manuscripts
        Contents (ordered according to numbers on the manuscripts): A lady of fashion [3] (3 p.). La belle conchita [5] (2 p.). La bicyclette [6] (2 p.). The waltz I heard in a dream [11] (2 p.) [at top of page 1: Berthe la sourde] [cue on p. 2 indicates Folk song follows]. Folk song [12] [vocal score] (4 p.) [p. 1 matches 5/127; p. 2-4 contain Peaceful theme]. The [angel (crossed out)] saint [16] (1 p.). A Boston schoolteacher [19] (2 p.). [1 page unidentified]
      - [Paris '90], 20 manuscript parts + 1 fragment; various sizes. (Box 6, Folder 131)
        Copyist's manuscript in ink, annotations in pencil, red pencil, and pasted on.
        Includes parts for: Fughetta [16B]. Berthe la sourde [16F]. A professor's wife. Avec mes sabots. [Order unknown: House (The house where I was born). Introd.]
      - [Paris '90], 1 manuscript part (14 p.); 34 cm. (Box 6, Folder 132)
        Copyist's manuscript in ink, annotations in pencil and red pencil.
        Note on page 1: Accordion solos from piano part (if we have time) Waltz (chorus (in E-flat or C Goulue about 20...24 bars Calliope once thru House where I was born A-flat or G (PP). (Peaceful Theme) 1 chourus For exit -play with piano -I will let you know where to play- (just a few spots) Nat....
        "Accordion for recording."
        Contents: Overture (3 p.). The angel (1 p.) Entr'acte I (3 p.). Laundress [includes Tourne mon moulin] (2 p.). Lend me a bob (2 p.). Entr'acte II (2 p.). Yvette (1 p.)
      - [Paris '90. (Sketches)], 18 leaves of music; various sizes. (Box 6, Folder 133)
        Badger-part 1 dated: Aug. 7.
        "Can-Can" dated: April 23, 1951.
      - [Paris '90. Angel] The angel (Paris '90) / Kay Swift., 1 manuscript vocal score (1 p.); 33 cm. (Box 6, Folder 134)
      - [Paris '90. Belle conchita], 1 manuscript piano score (3 p.); 35 cm. (Box 6, Folder 135)
        Holograph in ink, annotations in pencil, and pasted in.
        Incomplete, lacks p. 1-2.
      - [Paris '90. Berthe la sourde] Berthe la sourde / music and lyrics by Kay Swift., 1 manuscript vocal score (2 p.); 32 cm. (Box 6, Folder 136)
        Holograph in ink, annotations in pencil and blue ink.
        Note at top of page 1: Copy for Katherine.
      - [Paris '90. Berthe la sourde (Sketches)], 8 leaves of music (5 + 3); 32 cm. (Box 6, Folder 137)
        Copyist's manuscript in pencil and ink, annotations in red pencil.
        5 p. are manuscript score [top of page 1 numbered: 16F]
        3 p. are sketches.
      - [Paris '90. Boston schoolteacher], 2 manuscript piano scores (1 p., 1 p.); 32 cm., 32 cm. (Box 6, Folder 138)
        2 versions.
      - [Paris '90. Calliope] Calliope / music and lyrics by Kay Swift., 1 manuscript vocal score (5 p.); 32 cm. (Box 6, Folder 139)
      - [Paris '90. Calliope] Final chorus of "Calliope" with key change at close. / Kay Swift., 1 manuscript vocal score (3 p.): 32 cm. (Box 6, Folder 139)
      - [Paris '90. Calliope] Cue 22: Interlude: Calliope; arr. by Danny Mendelsohn., 1 manuscript vocal score (4 p.); 31 cm. (Box 6, Folder 140)
        Copyist's manuscript in pencil, annotations in pencil and red pencil.
      - [Paris '90. Calliope] Calliope / words and music by Kay Swift -- New York: Chappell, 1952., 1 manuscript vocal score (4 p.); 31 cm. (Box 6, Folder 141)
      - [Paris '90. Calliope, arr.] Calliope: from "Paris '90" / Kay Swift., 1 manuscript score (11 p.); 32 cm. (Box 6, Folder 142)
        Holograph in pencil, annotations in green ink.
        Incomplete, lacks all after p. 11.
        Arr. for: voice, piano I, piano II, double bass, and percussion.
        Incomplete second p. 9 laid in.
      - [Paris '90. Calliope, arr.] Calliope / Kay Swift (from "Paris '90"), 1 manuscript score (9 p.) + 2 manuscript parts; 36 cm. (Box 6, Folder 143)
        Arr. for: percussion, voice, piano, and double bass.
        Parts for: double bass and percussion.
        Parts are holograph (?) in ink.
      - [Paris '90. Calliope, arr.] Calliope / words & music Kay Swift; arr. W. Bolcom, 1986., 1 manuscript score (15 p.); 44 cm. (Box 6, Folder 143)
        Arr for: flute I, flute II + piccolo, oboe I, oboe II, clarinet I, clarinet II, bassoon I, bassoon II, horn I, horn II, trumpet I, trumpet II, trombone, percussion, harp, piano, voice, violin I, violin II, viola, violoncello, and double bass.
        Dated: 1986.
      - [Paris '90. Calliope (Sketches)], 6 leaves of music; various sizes. (Box 6, Folder 144)
      - [Paris '90. Duchess of Verprés], 1 manuscript piano score (2 p.); 32 cm. (Box 6, Folder 145)
      - [Paris '90. House where I was born] The house where I was born., 1 manuscript vocal score (3 p.); 32 cm. (Box 6, Folder 146)
      - [Paris '90. House where I was born] House where I was born / music and lyrics by Kay Swift., 1 manuscript part (1 p.); 35 cm. (Box 6, Folder 146)
        Bottom and verso of page 1 contain sketches for "Keep On Keeping On" (dated: June 13,'85) (see 9/284)
      - [Paris '90. Lady of fashion] En voiture (Paris chic), 1 manuscript piano score (1 p.); 19 cm. (Box 6, Folder 147)
        Printed on bottom of paper: Manufactured for George Gershwin.
      - [Paris '90. Lend me a bob till Monday] Lend me a bob (till Monday) / Kay Swift., 1 manuscript vocal score (2 p.); 35 cm. (Box 6, Folder 148)
        Holograph (?) in ink.
      - [Paris '90. Madame Arthur] Mme. Arthur [St Lazare (crossed out)]: Piano-solo + voice., 1 manuscript piano score (2 p.); 32 cm. (Box 6, Folder 149)
        Includes voice cues without text.
      - [Paris '90. Madame Arthur], 1 manuscript vocal score (1 p.); 35 cm. (Box 6, Folder 149)
      - [Paris '90. Overture] Overture ("Calliope") / Kay Swift., 1 manuscript piano score (4 p.); 32 cm. (Box 6, Folder 150)
        Holograph in ink, annotations in pencil and pasted in.
      - [Paris '90. Overture], 1 manuscript score (6 p.); 41 cm. (Box 26, Folder 716)
        Holograph (?) manuscript in pencil, annotations in pencil.
        Incomplete, lacks all after p. 6.
      - [Paris '90. Overture], 1 manuscript score (3 p.); 44 cm. (Box 26, Folder 716)
        Copyist's manuscript (possibly holograph) in pencil.
        Incomplete, lacks all after p. 3.
      - [Paris '90. Peaceful theme], 1 manuscript piano score (2 p.); 31 cm. (Box 6, Folder 151)
        On label: Full piano copy of 16D, (cue: It's from the dwarf.) Berthe La Sourde.
      - [Paris '90. Peaceful theme], 1 manuscript piano score (1 p.); 32 cm. (Box 6, Folder 151)
      - [Paris '90. St. Lazare] St. Lazare / Aristide Briant; Kay Swift., 1 manuscript vocal score (2 p.); 31 cm. (Box 6, Folder 152)
      - [Paris '90. Selections], 7 p. of musical cues; various sizes. (Box 6, Folder 153)
        Copyist's manuscript in pencil and ink, annotations in pencil, and red and blue pencil.
        Contents: Cue sheet. Tourne, mon moulin [9A]. Goulue cues [14A, 14B, 14C.]. Lion tmer [15A, 15B]. Lion tamer finale [15C]. Berthe la sourde [16F, 16G]. Berthe la sourde [16H, 16I].
      - [Paris '90. Tourne, mon moulin], 1 manuscript vocal score (3 p.); 31 cm. (Box 6, Folder 154)
        Copyist's manuscript in ink, annotations in pencil, ink, and red and blue pencil.
      - [Paris '90. Waltz I heard in a dream], 2 manuscript chorus scores (2 p., 2 p.); 31 cm. (Box 6, Folder 155)
        Copyist's manuscript in pencil, annotations in red pencil.
        Arrangement by Danny Mendelsohn.
        For girls I & II, Tenor, Baritone, and Bass.
      - [Paris '90. Waltz I heard in a dream] The waltz I heard in a dream / words and music by Kay Swift -- New York: Chappell, 1952., 1 vocal score (5 p.); 31 cm. (Box 6, Folder 156)
    - [Sarah was there. "Dark" theme for Sarah's entrance] "Dark" theme for Donna Sarah's entrance., 1 manuscript piano score (1 p.); 32 cm. (Box 6, Folder 157)
      Written for proposed musical based on four television scripts by George Oppenheimer (see 14/56)
    - [Sarah was there. Donna Sarah's recitative] Donna Sarah's recitative., 1 manuscript vocal score (1 p.); 32 cm. (Box 6, Folder 157)
      Stamped on bottom: Music and Lyrics by Kay Swift.
    - [Sarah was there. Donna Sarah's tango with Jerry Bergen] Donna Sarah's tango with Jerry Bergen., 1 manuscript piano score (1 p.); 35 cm. (Box 6, Folder 157)